(Man:)Uh, you, you want to see
James Cameron's kidney stone?
ALL:
Ooh.
(Man:)He was so happy after he passed
it, he gave me a Terminator.
(Leonard:)That is amazing.
(Leonard:)How long have
you been collecting?
(Man:)Ever since I was a kid,
(Man:)but, uh, I didn't really
get serious
(Man:)until William Shatner's
bladder infection.
(Sheldon:)What'd you get?
What'd you get?
(Man:)Well, he said it was a tribble.
(Man:)It could be a toupee,
(Man:)but either way,
it's pretty cool.
I-I would love to
see your collection.
(Man:)Anytime.
(Man:)Uh, I've got some cool stuff.
(Man:)When I first started,
(Man:)I thought it would be
a good way to meet women,
(Sheldon:)but, well, you know...
(Bernadette:)Sure.
Preach.
SHELDON: We know.
(Man:)Can I ask you
a personal question?
(Bernadette:)Sure.
(Man:)Um, I mean,
you're a guy like me,
(Man:)so how'd you get
a girl like Penny?